let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Which team does Ademola Lookman play for?",
        answer: "D. Atalanta",
        options: [
            "A. Rangers FC",
            "B. Manchester City",
            "C. Sunderland",
            "D. Atalanta"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Which country the highest AFCON cups?",
        answer: "B. Egypt",
        options: [
            "A. Nigeria",
            "B. Egypt",
            "C. Cameroon",
            "D. Morocco"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "In which of these years did Nigeria not win the AFCON cup",
        answer: "C. 2003",
        options: [
            "A. 1980",
            "B. 1994",
            "C. 2003",
            "D. 2013"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "What is the name of the President of Palestine?",
        answer: "B. Mahmoud Abbas",
        options: [
            "A. Benjamin Lewis",
            "B. Mahmoud Abbas",
            "C. Tajudeen Abbas",
            "D. Benjamin Netanyahu"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Who owns Tesla?",
        answer: "A. Elon Musk",
        options: [
            "A. Elon Musk",
            "B. Bill Gates",
            "C. Mark Zuckerburg",
            "D. Jeff Bezos"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Which national team does Jeremy Doku play for?",
        answer: "D. Belgium",
        options: [
            "A. Ghana",
            "B. Geramny",
            "C. Kenya",
            "D. Belgium"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "When was the first time Nigeria won the AFCON cup?",
        answer: "B. 1980",
        options: [
            "A. 2013",
            "B. 1980",
            "C. 1990",
            "D. 1994"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Which country hosted the 2010 World Cup?",
        answer: "D. South Africa",
        options: [
            "A. Belgium",
            "B. Russia",
            "C. Nigeria",
            "D. South Africa"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Who is the Commisioner for health in Anambra?",
        answer: "D. Afam Obidike",
        options: [
            "A. Anthony Ifeanya",
            "B. Paul Nwosu",
            "C. Peter Agu",
            "D. Afam Obidike"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Which Geoplitical Zone has the highest states?",
        answer: "A. North-West",
        options: [
            "A. North-West",
            "B. North-Central",
            "C. South-East",
            "D. South-West"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "When was Enugu state created?",
        answer: "C. 1991",
        options: [
            "A. 1987",
            "B. 1976",
            "C. 1991",
            "D. 1967"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "What is Novak Djokvic's ranking in Tennis?",
        answer: "A. World No. 1",
        options: [
            "A. World No. 1",
            "B. World No. 2",
            "C. World No. 5",
            "D. World No. 7"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "What is the name of the Ghanian Currency?",
        answer: "A. Cedi",
        options: [
            "A. Cedi",
            "B. Shillings",
            "C. Pounds",
            "D. Dinnars"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "Where is the headquarters of the United Nations?",
        answer: "C. New-york",
        options: [
            "A. Wakanda",
            "B. Paris",
            "C. New-york",
            "D. Manchester"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "In which year did Ghana gain their independence?",
        answer: "B. 1957",
        options: [
            "A. 2021",
            "B. 1957",
            "C. 1961",
            "D. 1991"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 16,
        question: "What is the Capital of Russia?",
        answer: "B. Moscow",
        options: [
            "A. Russia",
            "B. Moscow",
            "C. Harare",
            "D. Banjul"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 17,
        question: "When was ECOWAS founded?",
        answer: "C. 1975",
        options: [
            "A. 1980",
            "B. 1889",
            "C. 1975",
            "D. 1991"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 18,
        question: "Which country hosted the 2022 AFCON cup?",
        answer: "C. Cameroon",
        options: [
            "A. Nigeria",
            "B. South Africa",
            "C. Cameroon",
            "D. Ghana"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 19,
        question: "What was the first country to win the world cup?",
        answer: "B. Uruguay",
        options: [
            "A. Brazil",
            "B. Uruguay",
            "C. Italy",
            "D. Sweden",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 20,
        question: "What is Erling HAALAND's middle name?",
        answer: "C. Brawut",
        options: [
            "A. Josephi",
            "B. Jake",
            "C. Brawut",
            "D. Alfie"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 21,
        question: "What is Erling HAALAND's father's name?",
        answer: "D. Alfie",
        options: [
            "A. Josephi",
            "B. Jake",
            "C. Brawut",
            "D. Alfie"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 22,
        question: "Which month was Neymar born in?",
        answer: "C. February",
        options: [
            "A. December",
            "B. March",
            "C. February",
            "D. May"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 23,
        question: "A person living in a foreign country is called a/an?",
        answer: "A. Alien",
        options: [
            "A. Alien",
            "B. Citizen",
            "C. Lone-Wolf",
            "D. Natinonalist"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 24,
        question: "How many colours has the Nigerian Flag?",
        answer: "B. 2",
        options: [
            "A. 1",
            "B. 2",
            "C. 3",
            "D. 4"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 25,
        question: "Which of the following is a primary colour?",
        answer: "A. Blue",
        options: [
            "A. Blue",
            "B. Brown",
            "C. Green",
            "D. Purple"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 26,
        question: "The first muderer on earth was?",
        answer: "D. Cain",
        options: [
            "A. Judas Iscariot",
            "B. Abel",
            "C. Issac",
            "D. Cain"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 27,
        question: "The father of Abraham was?",
        answer: "C. Terah",
        options: [
            "A. Melcizedek",
            "B. Mathew",
            "C. Terah",
            "D. Methuselah"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 28,
        question: "The edo name for god?",
        answer: "C. Ubangiji",
        options: [
            "A. Amasheea",
            "B. Osanobua",
            "C. Ubangiji",
            "D. Sango"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 29,
        question: "Which month was Christiano Ronaldo born in?",
        answer: "C. February",
        options: [
            "A. December",
            "B. March",
            "C. February",
            "D. May"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 30,
        question: "Which team won the 20/21 champions league final?",
        answer: "B. Bayren Munchin",
        options: [
            "A. Real Madrid",
            "B. Bayren Munchin",
            "C. Liverpool",
            "D. Paris Saint-Germain"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 31,
        question: "In the bible who was cain's father?",
        answer: "D. Adam",
        options: [
            "A. Abraham",
            "B. Judas Isacriot",
            "C. Issac",
            "D. Adam"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 32,
        question: "The boling point of water is _____ degrees celcius?",
        answer: "B. 100",
        options: [
            "A. 50",
            "B. 100",
            "C. 0",
            "D. 200"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 33,
        question: "There are _____ states of matter?",
        answer: "B. 3",
        options: [
            "A. 4",
            "B. 3",
            "C. 2",
            "D. 1"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 34,
        question: "The freezing point of water is _____ degrees celcius?",
        answer: "C. 0",
        options: [
            "A. 50",
            "B. 100",
            "C. 0",
            "D. 200"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 35,
        question: "There are _____ states of matter?",
        answer: "B. 3",
        options: [
            "A. 4",
            "B. 3",
            "C. 2",
            "D. 1"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 36,
        question: "What is the capital of Ukraine?",
        answer: "B. Kylv",
        options: [
            "A. Beljing",
            "B. Kylv",
            "C. Cleveland",
            "D. New Delhi"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 37,
        question: "Which of these countries where not colonized?",
        answer: "D. Ethiopia",
        options: [
            "A. Brazil",
            "B. The United States of america",
            "C. Argentina",
            "D. Ethiopia"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 38,
        question: "Which of these countries is the largest in size?",
        answer: "A. Russia",
        options: [
            "A. Russia",
            "B. Greece",
            "C. Argentina",
            "D. Chad"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 39,
        question: "Which of these countries has French as her official Language?",
        answer: "B. Cameroun",
        options: [
            "A. Liberia",
            "B. Cameroun",
            "C. Ghana",
            "D. South Africa"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 40,
        question: "How many Local Government Areas are in Nigeria?",
        answer: "D. 774",
        options: [
            "A. 884",
            "B. 554",
            "C. 664",
            "D. 774"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 41,
        question: "The writer of the famous Things Fall Apart is",
        answer: "A. Chinua Achebe",
        options: [
            "A. Chinua Achebe",
            "B. Wole Soyinka",
            "C. John Clark",
            "D. James Clear"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 42,
        question: "In which of these cities was Jesus Christ cruxified?",
        answer: "D. Jerusalem",
        options: [
            "A. Bethlehem",
            "B. Nazareth",
            "C. Samaria",
            "D. Jerusalem"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 43,
        question: "Mohammed Ali was a very popular and successful ______?",
        answer: "D. boxer",
        options: [
            "A. footballer",
            "B. wrestler",
            "C. sprinter",
            "D. boxer"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 44,
        question: "The American professional, Tiger Woods is associated with _______",
        answer: "D. Golf",
        options: [
            "A. Badminton",
            "B. Rugby",
            "C. Table tennis",
            "D. Golf"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 45,
        question: "An octogenarian is one who has reached the age of _____?",
        answer: "A. eighty years",
        options: [
            "A. eighty years",
            "B. seventy years",
            "C. one hundred years",
            "D. fifty years"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 46,
        question: "The shortest month of the year is ______?",
        answer: "C. Februrary",
        options: [
            "A. January",
            "B. October",
            "C. Februrary",
            "D. September"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 47,
        question: "The Williams Sisters- Serena and Venus are associated with _______?",
        answer: "C. Lawn Tennis",
        options: [
            "A. Basketball",
            "B. Rugby",
            "C. Lawn Tennis",
            "D. Table tennis"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 48,
        question: "How many colours can be observed in a rainbow?",
        answer: "C. 7",
        options: [
            "A. 9",
            "B. 8",
            "C. 7",
            "D. 6"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 49,
        question: "Which team won the 22/23 champions league final?",
        answer: "B. Manchester City",
        options: [
            "A. Real Madrid",
            "B. Manchester City",
            "C. Liverpool",
            "D. Paris Saint-Germain"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 50,
        question: "Which of the following vehicles runs on iron tracks?",
        answer: "D. Train",
        options: [
            "A. Aeroplane",
            "B. Bicycle",
            "C. Motorcycle",
            "D. Train"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 51,
        question: "In which year did Nigeria become a republic?",
        answer: "D. 1963",
        options: [
            "A. 1960",
            "B. 1936",
            "C. 1989",
            "D. 1963"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 52,
        question: "The fastest land animal is the?",
        answer: "A. cheetah",
        options: [
            "A. cheetah",
            "B. lion",
            "C. tiger",
            "D. jaguar"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 53,
        question: "Who was the 44th president of America?",
        answer: "B. Barack Obama",
        options: [
            "A. Joe Biden",
            "B. Barack Obama",
            "C. Donald Trump",
            "D. Will Smith"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 54,
        question: "Who is the followed footballer on Instagram?",
        answer: "C. Christiano Ronaldo",
        options: [
            "A. Erling Haaland",
            "B. Kylain Mbappe",
            "C. Christiano Ronaldo",
            "D. Lionel Messi"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 55,
        question: "An adult human being should naturally have _____ set of teeth",
        answer: "A. 32",
        options: [
            "A. 32",
            "B. 28",
            "C. 1000",
            "D. 36"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 56,
        question: "The blood pumping station of the body is the _______",
        answer: "B. heart",
        options: [
            "A. kidney",
            "B. heart",
            "C. abdomen",
            "D. trachea"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 57,
        question: " Which of these is the organ of taste?",
        answer: "B. tongue",
        options: [
            "A. lips",
            "B. tongue",
            "C. gullet",
            "D. trachea"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 58,
        question: "Which English team is popular with the slogan: ‘Never Walk Alone’?",
        answer: "D. Liverpool",
        options: [
            "A. Aresnal",
            "B. Geneova",
            "C. Leister City",
            "D. Liverpool"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 59,
        question: "The picture displayed on the twenty Naira note is that of________.",
        answer: "B. Murtala Muhammed",
        options: [
            "A. Alvan Ikoku",
            "B. Murtala Muhammed",
            "C. Abubakar Tafawa Balewa",
            "D. Obafemi Awolowo" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 60,
        question: "An adult human being should naturally have _____ set of teeth",
        answer: "A. 32",
        options: [
            "A. 32",
            "B. 28",
            "C. 1000",
            "D. 36"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 61,
        question: "Which of these is a respiratory organ?",
        answer: "C. nose",
        options: [
            "A. skin",
            "B. tongue",
            "C. nose",
            "D. eye"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 62,
        question: " Which of these is not a human resource?",
        answer: "D. Automobile",
        options: [
            "A. Teacher",
            "B. Doctor",
            "C. Lawyer",
            "D. Automobile",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 63,
        question: "The fastest air animal is the ",
        answer: "B. Falcon",
        options: [
            "A. Crow",
            "B. Falcon",
            "C. Eagle",
            "D. Housefly"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 64,
        question: "The picture displayed on the ten Naira note is that of________.",
        answer: "A. Alvan Ikoku",
        options: [
            "A. Alvan Ikoku",
            "B. Murtala Muhammed",
            "C. Abubakar Tafawa Balewa",
            "D. Obafemi Awolowo" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 65,
        question: "How many weeks are there in a year?",
        answer: "A. fifty-two",
        options: [
            "A. fifty-two",
            "B. fifty-eight",
            "C. forty-six",
            "D. fifty-six"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 66,
        question: "Where is Usain Bolt",
        answer: "C. Jamaica",
        options: [
            "A. Kenya",
            "B. Ghana",
            "C. Jamaica",
            "D. USA"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 67,
        question: "Which of these animals is venomous?",
        answer: "C. scorpion",
        options: [
            "A. lion",
            "B. tiger",
            "C. scorpion",
            "D. lizard"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 68,
        question: "The first point of socialization is the",
        answer: "B. family",
        options: [
            "A. church",
            "B. family",
            "C. school",
            "D. playground"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 69,
        question: "The young of a whale is called a/an",
        answer: "B. calf",
        options: [
            "A. whaling",
            "B. calf",
            "D. dolphin",
            "D. kid"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 70,
        question: "The largest land animal is the",
        answer: "B. elephant",
        options: [
            "A. lion",
            "B. elephant",
            "C. whale",
            "D. giraffe"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 71,
        question: "The largest bird which cannot fly is the",
        answer: "A. ostrich",
        options: [
            "A. ostrich",
            "B. turkey",
            "C. chicken",
            "D. vulture"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 72,
        question: "Which of these is not a state in the Federal Republic of Nigeria?",
        answer: "D. Ekit",
        options: [
            "A. Delta",
            "B. Taraba",
            "C. Ondo",
            "D. Ekit"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 73,
        question: "Nigeria is situated in the ________ of Africa.",
        answer: "D. West",
        options: [
            "A. North",
            "B. East",
            "C. South",
            "D. West"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 74,
        question: "Which of these women fought against the killing of twins?",
        answer: "A. Mary Slessor",
        options: [
            "A. Mary Slessor",
            "B. Mary Anne",
            "C. Mary Magdalen",
            "D. Mary Jones"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 75,
        question: "Which of these countries has French as her official language?",
        answer: "B. Republic of Benin",
        options: [
            "A. Ghana",
            "B. Republic of Benin",
            "C. Kenya",
            "D. Egypt"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 76,
        question: " Dead bodies are kept in ______ before they are buried",
        answer: "C. Mortuaries",
        options: [
            "A. Asylums",
            "B. Graves",
            "C. Mortuaries",
            "D. Cold rooms"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 77,
        question: "Which country is the current football world cup champion?",
        answer: "B. Argentina",
        options: [
            "A. Spain",
            "B. Argentina",
            "C. France",
            "D. Croatia"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 78,
        question: "The capital of Taraba State is _________ .",
        answer: "B. Jalingo",
        options: [
            "A. Delta",
            "B. Jalingo",
            "C. Ondo",
            "D. Ekiti"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 79,
        question: "Which of these animals is poisonous?",
        answer: "C. scorpion",
        options: [
           "A. lion",
           "B. tiger",
           "C. scorpion",
           "D. lizard"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 80,
        question: "The best clothes to put on during the hot season is ___ clothes.",
        answer: "B. light white",
        options: [
           "A. light green",
           "B. light white",
           "C. long brownish",
           "D. thick dark"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 81,
        question: "The picture displayed on the five Naira note is that of________.",
        answer: "C. Abubakar Tafawa Balewa",
        options: [
            "A. Alvan Ikoku",
            "B. Murtala Muhammed",
            "C. Abubakar Tafawa Balewa",
            "D. Obafemi Awolowo" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 82,
        question: "Who is the most followed person on Instagram",
        answer: "A. Christiano Ronaldo",
        options: [
            "A. Christiano Ronaldo",
            "B. Mr. Beast",
            "C. Dywane Johson",
            "D. Elon Musk"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 83,
        question: "Who owns Space X?",
        answer: "A. Elon Musk",
        options: [
            "A. Elon Musk",
            "B. Bill Gates",
            "C. Mark Zuckerburg",
            "D. Jeff Bezos"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 84,
        question: "Who owns Facebook?",
        answer: "C. Mark Zuckerburg",
        options: [
            "A. Elon Musk",
            "B. Bill Gates",
            "C. Mark Zuckerburg",
            "D. Jeff Bezos"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 85,
        question: "In ancient history, a Pharaoh was a ruler in which country?",
        answer: "D. Egypt",
        options: [
            "A. Ghana",
            "B. Republic of Benin",
            "C. Kenya",
            "D. Egypt"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 86,
        question: "On which continent is the Sahara Desert?",
        answer: "C. Africa",
        options: [
           "A. Asia",
           "B. South America",
           "C. Africa",
           "D. North America"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 87,
        question: "How many states are in the South-east",
        answer: "A. 5",
        options: [
           "A. 5",
           "B. 6",
           "C. 7",
           "D. 19"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 88,
        question: "The #ENDSARS protest started in which state",
        answer: "B. Lagos",
        options: [
            "A. Abuja",
            "B. Lagos",
            "C. Port-Harcourt",
            "D. Enugu"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 89,
        question: "Who is the champion league’s top goal scorer of the 23/24 seson?",
        answer: "A. Erling Haaland",
        options: [
            "A. Erling Haaland",
            "B. Kylian Mbappe",
            "C. Kevin De Brunye",
            "D. Lautaro Martinez"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 90,
        question: "Who is the champion league’s top goal scorer of all time?",
        answer: "D. Cristiano Ronaldo",
        options: [
           "A. Zinedine Zidane", 
           "B. Thierry Henry",
           "C. Lionel Messi",
           "D. Cristiano Ronaldo"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 91,
        question: "How champions league trophies do Liverpool have",
        answer: "D. 5",
        options: [
            "A. 2",
            "B. 3",
            "C. 4",
            "D. 5"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 92,
        question: "God visited the Egyptians with ___ plagues",
        answer: "B. 10",
        options: [
            "A. 7",
            "B. 10",
            "C. 12",
            "D. 20"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 93,
        question: " Which team won the (2016/2017) EPL cup?",
        answer: "B. Leicester City",
        options: [
            "A. Liverpool",
            "B. Leicester City",
            "C. Chelsea",
            "D. Manchester City"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 94,
        question: " God created all that exists in ____ days.",
        answer: "C. 7",
        options: [
            "A. 12",
            "B. 10",
            "C. 7",
            "D. 5"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 95,
        question: "Which of these teams did Christtiano Ronaldo not play for",
        answer: "B. Al Hilal",
        options: [
            "A. Al Nassar",
            "B. Al Hilal",
            "C. Sporting CP",
            "D. Juventus"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 96,
        question: "The picture displayed on the hundred  Naira note is that of?",
        answer: "D. Obafemi Awolowo",
        options: [
            "A. Alvan Ikoku",
            "B. Murtala Muhammed",
            "C. Abubakar Tafawa Balewa",
            "D. Obafemi Awolowo" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 97,
        question: " An animal that lives on both land and water is called a/an",
        answer: "A. Amphibian",
        options: [
            "A. Amphibian",
            "B. Mammal",
            "C. Reptile",
            "D. Bird"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 98,
        question: "Which of the following are not canivours",
        answer: "A. Zebra",
        options: [
            "A. Zebra",
            "B. Lion",
            "C. Tiger",
            "D. Panther"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 99,
        question: "Which of the following was not part of the 12 apostles",
        answer: "D. Judah",
        options: [
            "A. John",
            "B. Andrew",
            "C. James",
            "D. Judah"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 100,
        question: "The first King of Isreal was",
        answer: "B. Saul",
        options: [
            "A. Solomon",
            "B. Saul",
            "C. David",
            "D. Samuel"
        ]
    }
]